Charu Bhagat

Automation Test Specialist

Almost 7+ years of experience in Testing - Manual and Automation for both Web and Mobile. 2+ years of experience in Salesforce. Good Cooperation in assisting with all the stakeholders to accomplish a milestone, Improve my skills and Contribute towards achieving the Organization's Objective.



cbhagat18389@gmail.com



+91-7042488876



Noida



linkedin.com/in/cbhagat

SKILLS

Selenium Webdriver

Mobile Testing

Appium

TestNG



ALM



Java

BDD Cucumber

Salesforce Testing

Oracle Testing

Zephyr Scale

Agile

REST Assured

Qmetry



Jenkins



Bitbucket

Git

Postman

Panaya

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Hindi

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

WORK EXPERIENCE

Test Specialist

IBM

09/2021 - Present

Brief Project Description

- DHL: Dalsey Hillblom Lynn is a German logistics company providing international shipping and courier services. Automated the important flows on Oracle Fusion Cloud ERP using Selenium, Java, TestNG, BDD Cucumber, ALM.
- MSIL: Maruti Suzuki India Limited is the largest automobile manufacturer in India, specialising in small cars. Worked on 3 all Regions India, Japan and Europe. Involved in Scripting and Executing the manual testcases on both IOS and Android Device using IBM IGNITE Quality Platform (IQP).
- CPC: Canada Post Coorporation operate a postal service for the transmission of messages, information, funds and goods and to provide other related services. Worked on Salesforce Customer Identity, Sales Cloud, Salesforce Maps where we need to create E2E automation scripts with different users like Sales Representative, Sales Manager in two languages like french and english. Tools Used- Selenium, Java, TestNG, BDD Cucumber, JIRA, Zephyr Scale.
- ERICSSON: Worked on E-Commerce Cloud, where the process is of buying the products and then evaluating the licenses accordingly. The various products involved here are: Products, Licenses, Accounts, Cases, Contacts, etc. Tested using various different users like Buyer, Operations, Product team member and Store Admin. Also tested on various different environments like: Dev, QA, Staging.
- SALESFORCE MY COMPASS: Automating the Basic functionalities of the Salesforce Application like Omniscripts and flex cards on Account 360 view using Selenium WebDriver, Java and TestNG framework. Running the Regression suites weekly. Also worked Manually in writing of the Test Cases and Executing them in Qmetry. Bug Tracking and Error Reporting. Followed Agile Methodology. Involved in technical discussions on data model of the objects, and Enabling Access to the users via OWD, Profiles and Permission Sets.

Technology Analyst Infosys Ltd.

08/2017 - 08/2021

Brief Project Description

- ESTEE LAUDER COMPANIES: Working in **UFT** to **Selenium** Migration Project where involved in creation of the test scripts. Automating **UFT** scripts to selenium scripts using **Selenium WebDriver**, **Java** and **testNG** framework. Completing the weekly assigned TC's in time. Setting up meetings for any Clarification from the Manual/Dev Team. Working on **Agile** Methodology and attending daily scrum calls
- ASIAN DEVELOPMENT BANK: Execution of the Test cases already written in Panaya and Automating some of the Regression test cases. Retesting Defects and Raising new Defects in Panaya. Retrieving Test Data from SQL. Automating some Regression TC's using Selenium WebDriver, TestNG, Java
- TELSTRA: Contributed in designing test cases manually and performed execution of the same. Writing TC's for internal tools like CNS-DI,MANAT in JIRA and executing the same. Retesting of the Bugs in JIRA and Re-execution of the related failed TC's. Clarification from the Developers for the bugs resolved in case of any confusion. Sending Daily Status Report to the Lead by EOD

CERTIFICATES

Infosys Global Agile Developer Certification

Infosys Certified Selenium Automation Tester Certification

EDUCATION

B.TechGalgotias University

2013 - 2017

Courses

CSE (CGPA: 7.87)

CERTIFICATES

Salesforce Certified Administrator

Salesforce Certified Platform App Builder

Salesforce Certified Service Cloud Consultant